



name Amanda Mercer
email amanda@amandamercer.ca
phone 905-439-2598
website amandamercer.ca
address 284 Oshawa Blvd S
Oshawa, ON
Canada, L1H 5S1

ABOUT ME

I am graduate from the joint Interactive Media Design program at Western University and Fanshawe College. Through this program I have had the opportunity to gain critical, theory-based knowledge about media, technology, advertising and marketing, as well as hands-on experience with coding, designing, editing and photography. I am an incredibly organized individual who loves working as part of a team as well as independently, and who never wants to stop learning and expanding my worldview.

PERSONAL SKILLS
Poor Exceptiona Teamwork
Creativity
Organization
Communication
Problem Solving
Work Ethic
Reginner Professional Web Design
CSS3
HTML5
JavaScript
PHP
jQuery
Laravel
Codelgniter
Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
After Effects

© OBJECTIVE

To obtain a fulltime position within an innovative digital communications agency where I will have the opportunity to develop efficient and intuitive user interfaces for web applications while continuing to learn and expand my knowledge of emerging web technologies.

EDUCATION

Fanshawe College

Diploma in Interactive Media Design 2014-2017 London, ON

Western University

B.A. in Media, Information and Technoculture 2013-2017 London, ON

EMPLOYMENT

Junior Front-end Developer — Vicimus

- Develop and execute provided creative ideas from static concepts to code
- Collaborate with designers while also interfacing with tech team to ensure both code quality and creative integrity is maintained and up to standard
- Take direction from the department head as well as work independently on projects within supplied requirements and timelines
- Work in a fast-paced, deadline based environment
- Proactively solve problems and provide solutions to overcome technical hurdles 2017 Toronto, ON

Back-end Developer — Reactr | Fanshawe College

- Worked independently and as a team on back-end of websites
- Took on different roles when needed, such as design and front-end development
- Updated supervisors on progress on daily basis through Slack (Scrum model)
- Learned new frameworks for projects (Laravel, Codelgniter)
- Had weekly meetings with supervisors to show progress

2016 - 2017 London, ON

Team Leader/Key Holder — Marble Slab

- Overlooked coworkers and kept them on task
- Maintained a steady and continuous workflow
- Consistently multitasked between serving customers, prepping food items, and fulfilling managerial duties
- Frequently opened and managed store successfully without supervision 2015 2016 Oshawa, ON

Shift Leader — Dairy Queen

- Overlooked coworkers and kept them on task
- Served customers in a professional and friendly manner
- Consistently multitasked between serving customers, prepping food items and cleaning prep areas

2011 - 2014 Courtice, ON

☆ HONOURS & ACHIEVEMENTS

Dean's Honour Roll

Fanshawe College 2014-2017 London, ON

Western Scholarship of Excellence

Western University 2013 London, ON

Yearbook — Greatest Contributor

Monsignor John Pereyma CSS 2013 Oshawa, ON

Ontario Scholar

Monsignor John Pereyma CSS 2013 Oshawa, ON